# **ANDREW KAN**

Arcadia, CA | 626-232-0108 | andrewjkan@gmail.com | www.andrewkan.com

## FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPER

Passionate and innovative front-end web developer dedicated on building and improving the performance of high traffic websites for global companies. Using technical, communicative, and problem solving skills to create enjoyable and fully optimized experiences for users on any platform.

## **EXPERTISE**

- Front-End Web Development
- Coding and Programming
- Responsive Development
- Cross-Browser Compatibility

- Site Troubleshooting
- Agile Development
- Scrum Methodologies
- UX & UI Design

# **TECHNOLOGY**

HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, SASS, ES6, PHP. React, AngularJS, Canvas, Bootstrap, Foundation, npm, git, SSH, Sourcetree. Sublime Text and Atom. Grunt, gulp, and webpack. Wordpress and Tumblr. Mac, Windows, and Linux. Adobe and Microsoft Suite.

#### **PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE**

# Front-End Web Developer | Nexon America

Sept. 2017 – Feb. 2018

Developed marketing websites and email campaigns for the global launch of HyperUniverse, Nexon's revolutionary side-scrolling battle arena game. Created an interactive website for Mabinogi, Chainslash. Utilized frameworks built within the company and worked with .NET Framework. Projects were built using build processors like Webpack and Gulp. All projects had to accommodate for localization.

# Web Developer | TVGla

Nov. 2014 – Aug. 2017

Created and updated promotional websites for one of TVGla's clients, Wheel of Fortune. Built pages and web applications that promoted episodes during the week. Successfully launched the official franchise website, Furious 7 ("1.516 billion in box-office sales"). Worked with other clients to build interactive website experiences. Collaborated with the team to build technical standards and advocated for process improvements. Estimated project timelines and communicated with vendors.

## **Web Developer** | Trigger LLC

Aug. 2013 – Nov. 2014

Developed various client websites and launched the franchise website for The Amazing Spider-Man 2 ("709 million" in box office sales"). Maintained the Trigger's corporate website. Assisted lead developers to finish high volume of projects. Built boilerplates and technical standards for the company. Worked with AngularJS and other JavaScript frameworks to build web applications.

## **EDUCATION**

The Art Institute of California | Bachelor of Science Degree in Web Design & Interactive Media

## **INTERESTS & RESEARCH**

Unity, Virtual Reality, Augmented Reality, WebGL, blockchain, and mobile application development.